indoarticles.com 2008-12-18

# Free Articles From IndoArticles.Com

IndoArticles.com Privacy Policy  
[Effective 10th. February, 2006]

_Subscription Forms_

IndoArticles.com uses subscription forms for individuals to request information by subscribing to Email Newsletters based on their categories of interest. We collect visitor's contact information (like your email address) to provide you with the information that you request. We will periodically send you email referring to news and updates to IndoArticles.com.

 _Choice / OPT-IN_

We provide opt-in opportunities for all email lists that you choose to receive. We use your email addresses to confirm your subscription and validity of the provided email address. Your reply to this email is necessary for completing your subscription to any email list.

 _IP address_

We use your IP address, browser type, domain names, and access times, operating system, country of origin, page views, and users sessions to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP, etc. address is used to gather broad demographic information.

 _Cookies_

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer. Our site only uses session ID cookies so our advertisement server can deliver proper ad rotation sequences. For example, if three banners are in rotation, the individual gets the proper rotation without duplicates. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personally identifiable information while on our site. Further, once a user closes their browser the cookie simply terminates.

 _Links_

This site contains links to other sites. IndoArticles.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. IndoArticles.com recommends you refer to each Network Member's Privacy Statements.

 _Sharing Information_

IndoArticles.com does not share, sell or rent your email addresses to outside third parties. Personally identifiable information will only be disclosed due to law or court demands (see our legal disclaimer below for more information)..

 _Supplementation of Information_

We do not supplement your personally identifiable information with any outside third parties information.

 _Correct / Update_

Change the email address that you have subscribed with by first unsubscribing with your current email address. Then, resubscribe with your new email address. All email list welcome messages contain the information necessary for subscription and removal from their appropriate list.

 _Unsubscribe_

We provide unsubscribe/opt-out opportunities for all email lists that you choose to receive. All email list welcome messages contain the information necessary for removal from the list. Removal from all lists is instant and automated by our servers.

 _Surveys_

The email addresses and contact information collected via publisher surveys are used solely to compile general statistical data. The users' personally identifiable information is never sold or given out to parties outside IndoArticles.com. All information is collected via the online form provided.

 _Notification of Changes_

IndoArticles.com will occasionally update our Privacy Policy based on our and users' feedback. If there are any material changes to how we use your personal information, we will notify via email and provide you the opportunity to opt-out prior to any substantial change that has been taken. However, if you have opted out of all communication from IndoArticles.com you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. IndoArticles.com encourages you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy.

 _Legal Disclaimer_

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

 _Contacting the Web Site_

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us here.
